Yauhen Varapayeu - Frontend Developer (React)

Tel.: +375447008632, e-mail: amidawolf@gmail.com, portfolio: https://awportfolio-site.netlify.app/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/evgeniy-voropaev-aw/

RSSchool: https://app.rs.school/cv/47d6664e-aad2-4312-80ec-760719fd196b

github - https://github.com/AmidaWolf

English: A2+ (https://www.efset.org/cert/Ra48Ur)

Summary of Qualifications

Start programming in 2019 after studying at RS School (JavaScript, React). Worked as a freelance web developer within a team of backend developer, designer and team leader. In 2022, I upgraded my skills at RS School (Typescript + React + Redux). Total experience 3 years. In high priority, looking for a full-time remote work.

Technical Skills

Programming languages and technologies: React, Redux, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS/SCSS

Programming practices: Agile, Kanban, Code review

Tools: GIT, Webpack, VS Code, Webstorm, Figma, Photoshop

Professional Experience

Freelance, 08.2019 - now

- Roles (from earliest to latest): Developer, Lead Developer, Team-Lead
- Responsibilities (from earliest to latest):
 - developing small elements and completed products, implement new functionality to existing projects, fixing bugs, making suggestions for improvement, communicating with the rest of the team
 - feature design, planning and splitting tasks into smaller ones, developing functional modules and whole products, creating a library of universal components, communicating with the rest of the team to refine features
 - o communicating with clients, choosing architectural solutions for projects from scratch, preparing a development base (webpack, prettier, eslint, etc.), creating tasks and separating responsibilities (Trello with Kanban), Code Review and refactoring assistance, developing functional modules (interaction with the server, authentication, saving and processing data) and whole products, helping students and transferring knowledge in RSSchool projects
- Technologies: HTML5/CSS3/JS, webpack/gulp, SCSS, React, Redux, styled components, TypeScript
- Achievements: in most projects, release dates were not violated, 20+ improvements for one of the projects (e-commerce) based on the results of communication with the customer, more than 20 thanks from students, several customers who switched to permanent service after the work was completed
- Other activities: non-stop self-education and self-improvement (RSSchool mainly), helping students and transferring their own knowledge in RSSchool projects, several pet projects, helping to improve the RSSchool educational platform

Irrelevant Experience

Architecture and Construction LLC, director, 05.2013 - now

Some projects

PMA - project management app

Project: https://pma-team38.netlify.app/

Source: https://github.com/Tianika/project-management-app/tree/develop

Position: lead developer

Environment: react, redux, axios, i18next

RSLang - web app for learning English

Project: https://rslang-amidawolf.netlify.app/ **Source:** https://github.com/AmidaWolf/rslang

Position: team lead, developer

Environment: JS, TypeScript, SCSS, webpack

ProjectInterClassic - architectural company site

Project: https://piklassik.com/

Position: developer

Environment: JS, CSS, Gulp

Hobby and fun weekend projects

Portfolio site

Project: https://awportfolio-site.netlify.app/

Source: https://github.com/AmidaWolf/react-portfolio

Position: developer

Environment: react with hooks, styled components

JJIT with local deploy

Source: https://github.com/ArchiKeV/jjit

Position: developer **Environment:** JS, CSS

Education

RSSchool JavaScript/Front-end (https://app.rs.school/certificate/tn7crqcd) - 09.2021 – 03.2022;

RSSchool React (https://app.rs.school/certificate/bupdbh09) - 03.2022 - 06.2022;

English: A2+ (https://www.efset.org/cert/Ra48Ur).